First class problems. Second class detectives.
Murder Mystery is a action, comedy, mystery film directed by Kyle Newacheck.
On a long-awaited trip to Europe, a New York City cop and his hairdresser wife
scramble to solve a baffling murder aboard a billionaire's yacht.
Nick Spitz, played by Adam Sandler.
Audrey Spitz, played by Jennifer Aniston.
Charles Cavendish, played by Luke Evans.
Malcolm Quince, played by Terence Stamp.
Grace Ballard, played by Gemma Arterton.
Tobey Quince, played by David Walliams.
Murder Mystery is a 2019 American comedy mystery film directed by
Kyle Newacheck and written by James Vanderbilt.
The film stars Adam Sandler, Jennifer Aniston, and Luke Evans, and follows a married
couple who are caught up in a murder investigation on a billionaire's yacht.
It was released on Netflix on June 14, 2019.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel, Murder Mystery 2, was released on Netflix on March 31, 2023.
The film explores themes of chase, cop, money, murder, monaco.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.